(Sheldon:)it's actually
extremely plausible.
(Leonard:)And your poll numbers
just keep dropping.
(Priya:)I want to catch up
with all of you,
(Priya:)but first I really
must visit the loo.
I'm going, too; I'll
show you where it is.
All right, this goes
without saying,
(Raj:)but I'm just going
to say it anyway.
(Raj:)Hands off my sister.
Why would I touch her? She's
covered with airplane germs.
(Raj:)I'm so not talking to you.
I'm talking to him.
(Howard:)Hey. I've got a girlfriend now.
Oh, please.
(Raj:)My sister's much hotter
(Raj:)than your girlfriend,
and you know it.
(Howard:)Let's just agree
they're both hot.
But dude, that's my sister
you're talking about!
(Howard:)Okay, forget who's hotter.
(Howard:)The first time Priya came to
L.A., Leonard and I made a pact
(Howard:)out of respect to our
friendship and to you
(Howard:)that neither of us
would hit on her.
Did you pinky-swear?
(Howard:)Yes.
(Raj:)Okay, then.
(Sheldon:)Cobbler. I'm still laughing.
(Priya:)It's really nice
to see you again, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Yeah. It's good
to see you, too.
(Leonard:)Here you go.
(Priya:)Thanks.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
(Howard:)Okay.